I had the picture diary between 2007 and 2010
So isch from being 12 until I was 16.
You could say that the picture diary was the Instagram of the time.
Although you were not as selective with what pictures you draw.
It was not uncommon for you to go for a school day,
Take Kamran, Foot Type 50 Photos,
Get home and upload everyone on the picture diary.
You had no barrier there.
Or was it so because I went in seven?
Anyway, the picture diary which is nowadays called Dayviews will close down.
Dayviews, the picture diary will not be advanced anymore.
... there will be no more I mean hi hi hi
So that's why I went in and saved every picture from 2007 to 2010.
And today I thought we would look at them.
A, what do you say?
I say we can start.
Ok, first picture.
Huh.
Hello and welcome to my picture diary from 2006 through - I lied to you.
August 16, 2006. Here I am 12 years old.
Here you also get a hint of what a fantastic taste I had in decor.
From being a kid, I had pink walls with big rabbit stickers like a board.
12-year-old Clara thought "No. That is baby wallpaper. Now I'm a big girl. Now I want other wallpaper.
Check this out!
Lime green wallpaper with such large pink flowers.
On the other hand, pink and lime green were my favorite colors.
I had to choose wallpaper all by myself.
Mama thought it was a bit crisp and encouraged me to choose this.
Since I also raised in a family that does not have so much money.
So the next time I tapyaized about my room then I was 18.
It was fun to bring so cool gymnies or the first date home.
What else do we have?
Hohohoho.
Creshing brills.
13 years I am here.
I have long hair and I have started to get quite a lot of pimples.
So my whole forehead was like a small hot tub.
I remember once when a girl in the class, so damn good, but she just like this:
"Ah Clara, you have something in the forehead."
And I thought inboard:
Ah I know.
Unfortunately, I can't just remove them.
And I then answered aloud:
"I know. My cat tore me."
Kungiiiiii
Ooooohoooooheho
Selfie session.
Here I am 13 years old.
Don't have as much pimples.
It may have been for periods.
I do not remember.
And it is also my acid, Kimberly who is 11.
I don't really know what to say about this picture.
I also do not know what it is we are looking at.
Because at this time you had like ... you couldn't see yourself in the camera.
At the same time, we are and we are very aware that we are footing ourselves.
It is a mystery.
And that is so bad.
I also thought I was pretty good at it.
Here I have made a little, a little more tan in the skin.
K. got red hair and I got brown hair.
We have both got brown eyes.
We also got whose little Kajallinije.
A. Nice stuff.
No but check!
Here I am at a Fridrot competition.
From the time I was twelve to being 18, I jumped high jump.
And I burned for it.
I loved high jump.
Please note the little tongue here.
I couldn't skip the bar without pray ...
This is Stockholm.
Please note the large Clara grill here and then there is a owed where Clara stands here.
And then Papa thought: "Clara, now we have to take a picture."
What else do we have?
Oh good God what is it?
I remember we sat and played mit you know with such IQ-test-Puzzle,
All pieces look different and so will get it together into a square.
We took these pieces and I threw them up in the air and my sister photographed when they fall down.
* sings* "I don't know who I am but I know I'm yours"
Here I have come second and third in some district championship I believe.
I think I have come second in high jump and third in hedge running.
Wooo, here I cut my hair short, God.
This is right at the beginning of nine.
And I cut off my hair.
This was the first picture I took on my hair too when I was on my way home from the hairdresser.
After all, it's not really a nice frill.
Again: Hair products.
In with some shit.
Because now it just hangs there, Clara, I asked it.
It was probably the same day when just cut it.
The snelog was fucking my best friend through high school.
I loved this hairstyle so hard.
It was damn the best thing I did when I was 16.
Again: Artsy image.
Black and white.
This was also when you started drawing mustaches on their fingers and prayed
Frock coat!
Sacre Coeur!
Je Suis Francaise!
Come over here and kiss my French lips!
Not this a frill that type all image teachers have?
Myyyy.
Check!
Also a hairstyle that is a bit on growth.
Damn.
I see the uncertainty in my gaze.
Did not like being in the picture at that time.
Little did I know that I would live on putting videos on myself on the internet.
If I had known it, I would have received heart fibrillation.
Friends, these were all pictures.
Now I have not shown it all because I have so very boring pictures on my picture diary.
But this was easy and most interesting.
But still fun.
Imagine that these pictures have put out on the internet for everyone's.
Ok friends, this was everything I had for this time.
Thank you for checking.
Don't forget to write comment, subscribe, share this vidon with friends!
So you can take it beautifully and then we will see you just as usual next Monday.
Bye.